and hopefully drive additional upsides. So I think that's a great story. And I would say also in
2027, we have a number of readouts, important readouts as well. Avalastimab in stroke
prevention, we will have as well the IELTS, no, we'll have as well the COSIMTA data as well as
some other phase two readouts as well as starting to read out as well our immune reset portfolio.
So I think a number of readouts coming that could further bolster the long-term out.
Very clear. Thank you very much. Thank you. Your next question comes from the line of
Kerry Holford from Barenburg. Please go ahead.
Thank you. A question for me on PluVicto, please. So following the recent European filing withdrawal
in that pre-taxing setting, just keen to hear whether you plan to run any additional trials
to address the EMA requirements. And if not, does the lack of a pre-taxing approval in that
region have any impact on your peak sales forecast for that drug?
Yeah, thanks, Kerry. So no impact on the peak sales forecast. We continue to expect $5 billion
plus. We had assumed all along that navigating the European feedback on the comparator arm would be
a challenge. We evaluated multiple ways to try to address it, and we tried to make the best
arguments that we could. But ultimately, we thought it was prudent at that point to withdraw.
We do see continued strong uptake in the vision population in Europe. It's important to note as
well in Japan and in China, we are able to both have the PSMA4 and PSMA vision,
which are critical, you know, long-term markets. And the next step now for Europe will be the
hormone-sensitive setting where we, because PluVicto is used in combination with an ARPI
versus an ARPI, there the comparator arm is what EMA would want. And I think would allow us then
if we're to move forward now, we have the strong, as you know, RPFS data. We're waiting on the OS
data. Once we have that OS data, we should be able to file in Europe and then expand the patient
population there. So I think that was the last question. I think that was the last question.
Well, best outcome, we decided rather than running additional studies, it would take many years
to just withdraw the file and wait for the HSPC readout.
Lovely. Thank you.
Thank you. Your next question today comes from the line of Steve Scaler from TD